For the record with comedian, actor, my friend, Leonard Robinson.
What is a song that describes your HBCU experience?
Right out the gate, probably like, all I want to do is a zoom, zoom, zoom, and a boom, boom.
What is a song that describes or reminds you of your time on Insecure?
Probably Whitney Houston.
What is it?
Give me one moment in time.
Why?
You know why that song for Insecure for me, it was like, because I saw, you know, I watched
the web series, and then when I read it, it was going to be a pilot.
I was like, ooh, I want to get in on that.
I feel like this is going to be something.
And then just my journey, like from testing from the pilot to not getting it to, you know,
them calling me back and trying to find a role, and then finally coming in on season
three, and then it was like one of the few times in my career thus far where I've kind
of tried to manifest something, and it actually turned around in a way a little bit better
than I thought it would have been.
We are, we are, we are.